Why're you asking about The Dollars?
どうしてダラーズのことなんか 聞くんだ？
You're not thinking of joining The Dollars, are you?
お前 まさかダラーズに入りたいなんて思ってる？
Whaaaat's thaaaat?!
なんだぁ そりゃあ～～!?
Why is my head on someone else's body anyway?!
そもそも なんで私の首に私以外の体があるんだ!?
Maybe it found a newly dead corpse.
出来たてホヤホヤの死体があったとか
I can't wait!
楽しみだなぁ 楽しみだなぁ 楽しみだなぁ！
What do you think will happen to us if the police get wind of this?
もし あれが警察の目に触れでもしたら 私たちはどうなると思う？
I don't care whether she dies or not. Depending
on the circumstances, dispose of her on the spot.
生死は問わないわ 場合によってはそのまま処理してしまいなさい
I guess my budget's pretty tight this month after all.
やっぱり 今月はちょっときついなぁ。
Now all I need is a kitchen sponge and...
あとは台所のスポンジと
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました～
The black bike!
黒バイクだ！
It should be right around this corner!
あの角を曲がったらいるはず
痛っ！
Owowowow...
痛ててて…
Um...I'm so sorry.
す… すみません 大丈夫ですか？
Are you all right?
You're...
あっ 君は…
Help me!
助けて！
Please!
お願い！
きゃあ～ 黒バイ！
The black bike!
Just what is that!? It's totally cool!
何これ 超カッケ～！
Can we take a picture?
写メるっしょ 写メるっきゃないっしょ！
Here we go!
This is awesome!
マジパネェんっすけど～！ やっべ～！
This picture's insane!
So the beautiful girl you bumped into on the
corner was being chased by some bad guy on a bike...
道の角でぶつかった美女が
バイクに乗った悪党に追われていて しかも記憶を失っており
...she's lost her memory...
...and she already fell asleep due to exhaustion by the time I got here.
オレが駆けつけた段階では疲れて眠っている
So you expect me to believe this dream you had, which in many ways isn't very dreamy.
そんな いろいろな意味でドリーマーな夢物語をオレに信じろと？
It's true, so I can't change it.
事実なんだから しかたないよ
It'd be better if this made you late for school in the morning.
これで 時間が朝の遅刻ぎりぎりタイムならベターだったんだがな
And it'd be marvelous if she were a transfer student.
あと その女が転校生ならマーベラス
Also, if she were a queen and your childhood friend, it'd be perfect.
そのうえ どっかの王女で 実はお前の幼なじみならパーフェクトだ
Ah, did you notice my pun on "better" and "clichéd?"
あっ 今のベタとベター掛けてることに気づいた？
I think it makes the joke even worse when you have to point it out.
それをわざわざ人に言うのがいちばん寒いと思う
I don't know what to do, since not only has she
lost her memory, but I can't even go to the police.
記憶がないうえに警察はダメだって言うもんだから
僕 どうしたらいいか分からなくてさ
All we can do is see how things develop.
様子見るしかねぇだろ
For now, we'll wait until tomorrow,
and then ask her all about her situation.
とりあえず 明日まで待って
それからのことは彼女の話をじっくり聞いてからだな
Okay.
うん
See you tomorrow.
んじゃ 明日な
うん 夜中にありがとう
Thanks for coming this late.
The black biker might remember my face.
黒バイクに顔を覚えられたかもしれない
The black biker of urban legend...
都市伝説と呼ばれる 黒バイク
What am I doing by making an enemy of her?
あれを敵に回して 僕に何ができるんだろう
I hated normal things.
普通のことが嫌いだった
Good morning.
I wanted to live a different life from other people.
人とは違う生き方がしてみたかった
Those feelings may have led me to get involved with this girl.
そんな気持ちから彼女をかくまってしまったのかも
There's only one thing Kida doesn't know.
一つだけ 紀田君の知らないことがある
It's about that wound on her neck.
彼女の傷のこと
It looks like her head was chopped off
with a saw and then forcefully reattached.
まるで ノコギリで 一度首を切ってから
無理やりつなぎ合わせたような…
This is an announcement from the school store:
売店より お知らせです
Our stock of jumbo melon bread has sold out for the day.
本日のジャンボメロンパンは売り切れました
Wow, Mikado!
おう 帝人～！
How's the sleeping beauty at your apartment doing?
眠れるアパートの美女 どうなった？
Kida?! Shh! Shh!
紀田君… しぃ！ しぃ～！
What's this about a beautiful girl?
何よ？ 何よ？ 美女って
I like hearing about that kind of thing.
オレ そういうの 反応 早いよ～
Actually, when Mikado turned a corner, he bumped into this girl with amnesia who was being chased by an evil person...
実は～
帝人が道を曲がったら
悪漢に追われる記憶喪失の美女とぶつかって～
And so, now he's living with a cute girl!
今 こいつは美女と暮らしてるってわけよん
C'mon, now. That's just a dream Kirigamine has.
なんだよ 霧ヶ峰の願望かよ～
Uhh, umm, err, it's Ryugamine.
あっ いや… 竜ヶ峰…
Anyone want to sell me their extra meal tickets?
ああ～
誰か余った食券買わねぇ？
No one will believe it, so it's okay.
なっ？ 誰も信じないから 大丈夫だって～
Anyway, what's up with the girl?
で どうしてる？ 美女
She was still asleep when I left this morning.
朝 出るときはまだ寝てた
Getting her beauty sleep, I bet.
美女爆睡だな～
Alright, let's get down to business.
まっ そんじゃあ 本題に入ろう
What business?
本題？
This is what I've been doing during lunch break and
it's the reason why I ate my lunch during fourth period.
このオレが４限に早弁までして
昼休みを有効に使おうとしている理由はずばりこれなわけよん
"Who's in The Dollars?"
「ダラーズ度予想」…
This is a pretty popular fad amongst our classmates, you know.
今 うちのクラスでちょっとしたブームなんだな これが
Everything about The Dollars is shrouded in mystery.
ダラーズの全貌は謎に包まれている
So, if someone in school says, "Hey, doesn't
that dude look kinda like he'd be in The Dollars?"
そこで 学校の中で「あいつ 雰囲気がダラーズっぽくね？」ってヤツに
I get them to vote for that person.
一票を投じるお遊び
Wow, it looks like there's a real consensus.
へえ～ 結構票がかたまってるんだ
That's because one person can vote for multiple people.
一人で何人でも投票できるからな
Huh? Takiguchi from class 1-D only has one vote.
あれ？ この１ーＤの滝口って人 一票しか入ってない
So you noticed?
気づいてくれた？
And who voted for him? None other than me, Kida Masaomi.
その一票 誰あろう
この紀田正臣の一票
My class has P.E. with his, and I'm sure he has to be in The Dollars.
オレ 体育で そいつのクラスと一緒なんだけど
滝口亮は間違いなく ダラーズだと思う
Why do you say that?
なんでそう思うの？
Intuition.
勘
ははっ…
On that note, I'm going to see if I'm right.
ってことで～ 今から確かめに行く
Wait!
ちょっと！
Excuse me!
すみませ～ん！ 滝口亮君いますか～？
Is Takiguchi Ryo here?
No, he's not.
いないよ
He in the cafeteria?
って 食堂？
さあ？ 屋上じゃねぇ？
I dunno. Probably on the roof.
He goes up there a lot during lunch.
あいつ 昼休みはよく上行ってるみたいだから
Ryo must take his smoke breaks up there.
亮君は上でスモーキングタイムかな？
Don't you think you should leave him alone?
や… やめた方がよくない？
There might be a lot of scary people up there.
怖そうな人とかいるかもしれないし
That was a joke.
冗談だよ
Smoking on the roof during lunch only happens in old, clichéd manga.
昼休みに屋上でスモーキングなんて
昔のベタな漫画じゃん
But I doubt he'd tell you the truth if you just
go up to him and ask, "Are you in The Dollars?"
けど いきなり「ダラーズですか？」なんて聞いても
ほんとのこと言ってくれないと思うし…
Just leave it to me.
任せときなって
I have an idea.
考えがある
Ummm...
Oh?
He...He's smoking...
ス… スモーキン…
Hey, Takiguchi!
お～い 滝口～！
Yo.
うぃっす
Hey.
Oh?
Wow, you write songs?
へえ～ 滝口って 曲作るんだ
Huh? Oh, yeah...
まあな
What's up?
で どうした？ なんか用か？
You need to talk to me?
There's something I want to ask.
聞きたいことがある
Shoot.
言ってみな
こほん…
Are you in The Dollars?
あなたはダラーズですか？
ちょっ… 紀田君 何を！
Kida, what're you...?
Yeah, I am.
ああ そうだけど
I knew it.
やっぱりな～ 絶対そうだと思ったんだ
I just knew you had to be.
See? My intuition is 100% perfect.
なっ？ オレの勘 百発百中～
He's my childhood friend.
こいつ オレの幼なじみ
Uhh, err, umm, I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
竜ヶ峰帝人です
So you're that famous guy.
あんたがあの有名人か
Huh? Famous guy?
えっ 有名人？
Your name.
名前がな
Want some?
食う？
ああ どうも
Thanks.
ん
Thank you.
サンキュー
Um, Takiguchi...
あの～ 滝口君
Why did you join The Dollars?
どうしてダラーズに入ったの？
I don't really know how to answer that question.
そう改めて理由を聞かれると 困っちゃうなぁ
I guess it was six months ago.
半年くらい前かな
I got an invite from someone I didn't know.
知らないヤツから誘いのメールが来てさ
It said, "The Dollars don't have any rules or regulations."
ダラーズにはなんのルールも拘束もないっていうんだ
At first I thought there's no way a group like that
could exist, but then I figured it'd be interesting if it did.
最初はそんなチームあるわけねぇって思ったんだけど
でも もしほんとにあるならおもしろいかなって
I don't like either giving or taking orders.
オレさ 誰かに命令するのも されるのも好きじゃねぇんだ
So, what kind of group is it?
で ダラーズってさ どんなチーム？
If I had to say, I guess they're "clearly colorless."
あえて言うと 無色透明って感じかな
"Clearly colorless?"
無色透明…
Yeah, they don't try to get as many members to wear the same colors as
possible and have power struggles like The Yellow Scarves or The Blue Squares.
黄布賊とか ブルースクウェアみたいに
同じ色の群れを増やして 勢力を競い合うってこともないしな
Who're The Blue Squares?
ブルースクウェアって？
They're a color gang that was around when I was in middle school.
オレが中学のとき全盛だったカラーギャング
I don't know much about them, but apparently
they caused some incident and broke up.
オレもよく知らないけど
なんか事件を起こして 壊滅したらしい
Kida?
紀田君？
So, you like The Dollars, Takiguchi?
じゃあ 滝口はダラーズが気に入ってんだ？
Yeah.
ああ
Do you meet with the other members?
ほかのメンバーとかにも会うの？
We only know each other's handles, so...
メンバーっつっても ハンドルしか分かんねぇしな
But I have met some.
けど 何人かには会ったぜ
Like at my part-time job or around town.
バイト先とか 街とかで
They've all been coincidental, though.
偶然だけど
Somehow, you just know that they're members.
なんとなくっぽいなって思ったら そうって感じかな
What kind of people are they?
例えば どんな人？
They are who they are, so you'll have to ask them, like you did me.
それはそいつのことだから
聞いてみろよ オレに聞いたみたいに
I bet most of them would answer you.
大抵答えると思うぜ
Aw, crap.
あっ やっべ
See you!
おっ先～！
Ever since I found out that Takiguchi was a
real Dollar, I decided I wouldn't tell anybody.
僕は滝口君が本物のダラーズだと分かったときから
誰にも言わずにおこうと思っていた
I figured that Takiguchi wouldn't want people making a fuss over it.
そういうことで騒がれるのは滝口君もきっと嫌だろうと思う
Okay, everyone, let's begin.
I assumed that only the people who asked needed to know.
聞いた人だけが知ってればいいと思った
Stand.
起立
Bow.
礼
That's all for our class representatives meeting.
以上で 代表委員会を終わります
I wonder if Kida's still doing stuff for the disciplinary committee?
紀田君 風紀委員の方まだやってるかな？
He'll probably be done soon.
たぶん もうすぐ終わるんじゃないでしょうか
Wait!
Harima Mika, the girl stalking Yagiri Seiji, has been
missing ever since the day before the entrance ceremony.
矢霧誠二君のストーカーだった張間美香さんは
入学の前日から失踪したままだった
Did you learn anything regarding Harima's whereabouts after that?
その後 張間さんのこと 何か分かった？
No, nothing.
いえ 何も…
Ryugamine!
竜ヶ峰～！
Kida says to go home without him!
紀田が先に帰ってくれってよ～！
Eh? What's keeping him?
ええ～ 紀田君 どうかしたの？
Apparently he's in the middle of a heated
debate with the disciplinary committee.
なんかさ 風紀委員会で大激論を繰り広げてるらしいぜ
See you.
それじゃあな～！
Umm...
えっと… じゃあ 行こっか
Shall we go?
Okay.
はい
I wonder what Kida's debate is about...
紀田君 何を激論してるんだろうね
Uh, maybe it's about the dress code or hairstyles.
やっぱり 服とか髪とかかな
Mikado!
帝人～！
I'm going to ask you all about that beautiful girl!
美女の話 よ～く聞くんだぞ～！
Introduce me to her sometime!
今度 オレのことも紹介しろよ～！
Snap!
びしっ！ じゃあね！
Later!
Th-That beautiful girl he's talking about is a
French person we met at Russia Sushi, and...
ビ… ビジョウさんって 「露西亜寿し」で会ったフランスの人で…
H-H-Her nose is pierced!
は… は… 鼻… 鼻にピアスをして～
And so Kida must be debating nose piercings!
紀田君はきっと鼻ピアスについて激論してるんだね～
I actually knew about you a long time ago, Ryugamine.
私 本当はずっと前から竜ヶ峰さんのこと知ってたんですよ
Huh?
When I passed in my matriculation forms,
there was a checklist on the receptionist's desk.
入学届を出すときに
受付に名前をチェックする一覧表みたいなのがあって
I thought your name was cool, and I
noticed someone had checked it off already.
そこで 格好いい名前だなって思ってたら
ちょうど そこにチェックした人がいて
Now I get to be a class representative with you...
そうしたら その人と一緒にクラス委員をやることに…
Wait!
ちょっと待った
Doesn't this sound a lot like what happened
between Harima Mika and Yagiri Seiji?!
これって張間美香さんと矢霧誠二君のパターンに似てない？
I don't want a stalker!
まずいよ ストーカーなんて
Wait, maybe it's okay since she's so cute.
いや こんなかわいい子ならありなのか？
No, wait, it's totally not!
いや 待て待て なしだろう
If things go bad...
下手すれば…
Sh-Sh-She'll stab me!
さ… さささ… 刺される!?
Fire!
I-I-I might be killed!
いや 放火されるかもしれないし
Wait, maybe she'd take my parents hostage!
待て待て 家族を人質に取られたら…
But if she has a good personality,
then it might not matter that she's a...
でも いい性格だったら ストーカーでもいいんじゃ…
Wait, stalkers don't have good personalities!
いや 待て ストーカーする時点で性格よくないし！
That was a joke.
冗談ですよ
Eh?
It'd just cause trouble for you if someone like me were following you around.
私みたいなのに付きまとわれたら迷惑ですよね
Um, that's not...
いや…
Don't worry.
安心してください 私はストーカーじゃないですから
I'm not a stalker.
Uh, umm, err, well...
あっ いや その…
I'm sorry.
ごめん
No, I'm the one who was teasing you.
いや からかったのは私なんですか
Please, don't apologize.
謝らないでください
Uh!
Um!
あの…
いや…
Well...
その… こ… これからもよろしく
I-I hope we work well together!
I hope so, too.
私の方こそ よろしく
Huh?
That's him, Takeshi! That's him!
タケシ
こいつだよ こいつ！
Who does she mean by "him?"
誰だろう？ 「こいつ」って 僕じゃないよね？
It's not me, is it?
お前だよ お前！
I mean you! It's you!
Why are you ignoring us?!
何シカトしてんだよ！
Umm...who might you be?
あ… あの～どちらさまでしょうか？
I had to buy a new cell phone, thanks to your friend!
お前の知り合いの お陰で私は新しい携帯を買ったんだ！
Uhh...I don't really understand what you're saying...
え～っと ちょっと意味がよく分かりませんが…
So, you're friends with the guy who broke my girlfriend's cell?
おめぇ オレの彼女の携帯ぶっ壊したヤツのダチなんだってなぁ？
Well, I wouldn't really call him my friend...
いや… 友達というほどの間柄では…
Then what is he? Your parent?! A cosigner?! Huh?!
じゃあ なんだよ？ 親か？ 連帯保証人か？
I think your assumptions are a tad biased...
そ… その推理には偏りがあるかと
Huh?!
Are you trying to lecture me!?
お前 オレに説教する気か？
Huh?!
You want me to teach you how to act towards your elders—
てんめぇ 上下関係ってものを教えて…
Huh?!
How commendable of me to say, "My hobby isn't punching girls."
オレが女の子を殴る趣味がないからって
なんて殊勝なんだろう
I'd like you to be my girlfriend, but I'm sorry.
彼女にしたいけど…
ごめん 君 タイプじゃないから
You're not my type.
Go home!
帰れ！
You're horrible!
ひどいよ～！
See you again!
まったね～
Well now, Ryugamine Mikado, I've been hiding
behind the school gate because I wanted to see you.
さて 竜ヶ峰帝人君
オレは君に会いたくて 校門の所に隠れて待ってたんだ
I have some business with you.
ちょっと用があってね
By the way...
ところでさ なんで黒バイクがいるの？
Why's the black biker here?
She's searching for the girl!
彼女を捜してるんだ
ああ～ 忘れてた～！
I forgot!
S-Sorry, but I'm in a hurry!
す… すみません 今日はちょっと急ぐので
See you later, Sonohara.
じゃあ 園原さん 僕はこれで
This is too surreal.
シュールすぎる
Anyway, these people will definitely follow me back to my apartment.
でも このままじゃ 間違いなくこの人たちは家まで ついてくる
So then...
そしたら…
Help me!
助けて！
Uh, umm...
あ… あの… その～
Well...
If you want to talk with me, let's do it here.
用件があるならここで伺いますが
I'll talk with you after the black biker's done.
オレの用は黒バイクのが済んでからでいいや
Hello?
もしも～し いつもお世話になっております
Thanks for your continued patronage.
Th-There's something I'd like to ask you.
お… お聞きしたいことがあります
What is it?
なんだ？
She'll listen to me?
意思の疎通ができるんだ
Um...just who are you?
あの… あなたは何者なんですか？
I'm looking for the daughter of one of my relatives.
I found her yesterday, but she ran away for some reason.
She...She's horrible at lying.
う… うそが 下手すぎる
S-Sorry, but I don't believe you.
す… すみません 信じられないです
How much do you know about me?
君は私のことをどれだけ知っている？
You're somewhat of an urban legend...
あの… あなたは都市伝説の一種で
You ride a bike with no headlights that doesn't make any noise...
エンジン音がしない ヘッドライトのないバイクに乗っています
And...
それで…
There are rumors you have no head.
あなたには首がないと
Do you believe that?
君はそれを信じているのか？
Um, could you let me see inside your helmet?
あの… 見せてくれませんか？
そのヘルメットの中を
I never thought I'd be able to ask that.
自分でもそんなことが聞けるなんて思ってもいなかった
Promise you won't scream?
絶対に悲鳴を上げたりしないか？
However, I felt like I'd been waiting a long time...
でも もうずっと以前から
こんなふうな瞬間が来るのを待っていたような気がした
For this moment.
I still don't know how to describe the way I felt at that time.
そのときの気持ちをなんて言えばいいのか 今も分からない
I just kept repeating, "Ah, I knew it. I knew it," in my heart.
僕は 胸の中で ただ ああ… やっぱり やっぱりと 繰り返していた
Th-Th-Thank you very much.
あ… ありがとうございます
After that, the legendary black biker told
me the real reason she was chasing that girl.
その後 伝説の黒バイクは 昨日 あの人を追っていた本当の理由を 話してくれた
She was a dullahan named Celty...
自分がセルティという名のデュラハンであること
She came to Japan in search of her stolen head...
奪われた首を追って 日本に来たこと
And the girl with stitches on her neck has a face that looks exactly like hers.
首に縫い目のある人がセルティさんの顔と瓜二つなこと
Normally, every part of that story would be unbelievable.
普通なら 何もかも信じられないような話だけど
But, mysteriously enough, I believed every single word of it.
僕は不思議とその言葉はすべて真実だと思えた
Are you her friend?
君はあの子の友達なのか？
No, I just met her yesterday.
いえ 僕も昨日知り合ったばかりなんです
I asked her a bunch of different things, but...
いろいろ聞いたんですけど 彼女記憶を失ってるみたいで
It seems she lost her memory.
Celty?
セルティさん？
Would you let me see her?
その子に会わせてもらえないか？
It's probably because you suddenly
started chasing her, but she's afraid of you.
たぶん いきなり追いかけられたせいだと思いますけど
彼女はセルティさんのことを怖がっています
I need to see her, no matter what!
私はどうしてもあの子に会いたい
Could you do something to help clear up this misunderstanding?
なんとかして誤解を解いてもらえないか？
I understand.
分かりました
Fruit milk in the afternoon is the best.
昼はフルーツ牛乳に限るぜ
I think this development's a sign that Biribiri's going to be the heroine!
やっぱ オレ この展開はビリビリ ヒロイン化の兆しだと思うんっすよね～！
No way! I bet the heroine's a princess goddess!
いやいやいや むしろ ヒロインは姫神で決まりっしょ！
くっそ… なめてんじゃねぇぜ
Hey!
What're you doing?!
何やってんだ お前！
Those bastards...shot a pebble...
あの野郎 小石を…
Eh?
They shot a pebble into my car!
小石をぶつけやがった～?
Calm down, Togusa!
落ち着け 渡草！
I'll never forgive them!
許さねぇぞ あの野郎～！
The light's red!
信号 赤 赤！ 赤～?
It's red! It's red!
Please wait here a bit.
ここで少し待っててください
I'll explain everything to her.
僕が彼女に事情を説明します
I don't want her to think I betrayed her if she sees you first, Celty.
先にセルティさんの姿を見られて
僕が裏切り者だと思われるのは嫌ですから
I understand.
了解した
He's a pretty cautious kid.
結構慎重な坊やじゃないか
Huh?
あれ？
That's the first time I've ever heard your name.
オレ あんたの名前初めて聞いたよ
I didn't know you were a foreigner.
外国人だとは思わなかったなぁ
You liar.
うそつけ
I'm not going to let it slide the next time you throw a rock at my horse.
こんど 私の馬に石をなげたらただではおかないぞ
Eh? So that's a horse?
へえ～ 馬なんだ～ それ
Despite the situation, isn't he a bit slow?
それにしてもさ ちょっと遅すぎないかなぁ？ 彼
Why's there a cleaning crew at this run-down apartment?
こんなボロアパートに清掃業者？
It couldn't be...!
まさか！
That's why we want to know where that girl you were with went.
だからよ にいさんがかくまったっつう女がどこ行ったのか
それが知りたいわけよ
This hair I found on your futon is from a girl, isn't it?
布団にあったこの髪の毛 女のもんだよなぁ？
I-I really don't know!
ほ… ほんとに知らないんです
P-Please...Please have mercy on—
か… 勘弁… 勘弁してください…
You've seen our faces.
お前には顔見られちまったしなぁ
We don't mind killing you right here.
この場で始末してやってもいいんだぜ
Hey, someone's coming!
おい 誰か来るぞ
I-I-I'm saved...
た… た… 助かった
You don't have to go after them.
追いかけなくていい 出どころは分かってる
I know where they're going.
I remember the van.
バンに見覚えがある
They're probably from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
あれはたぶん「矢霧製薬」の連中だな
Yagiri...Pharmaceuticals?
矢霧… 製薬？
Yep.
そっ 最近落ち目で
They're a puppet company that hasn't been doing well lately, so they're on the verge of being absorbed by a foreign firm.
外資系に吸収される寸前のでく会社
A girl who lost her head,
いなくなった首の女
A dullahan,
デュラハン
Gone missing,
行方不明
張間美香
Harima Mika,
Yagiri Seiji,
矢霧誠二
Human trafficking,
人買い
And The Dollars.
そして ダラーズ
What's he planning on starting?
何を始める気だ？
I was tired of normal things.
普通のことが嫌だった
Honestly, I half-assumed he was.
正直疑い半分だったんだが
Please.
お願いです 少しの間 私に協力してください
Even if it's only for a short while, please cooperate.
I wanted to live a different life from other people.
人とは違う生き方をしてみたかった
This evening, the ball is in my court.
駒は私の手の内にあります
That's why...
だから…
Jackpot!
大当たりだ
I...
僕は…
制作：lastzzz 安静の云 akira アキラ
I was tired of normal things.
普通のことが嫌だった
I wanted to live a life different from other people.
人とは違う生き方がしてみたかった
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs/
I can't believe that simple wish changed the destinies of so many people.
たった それだけのことが
こんなに大勢の人たちの運命にかかわってくるなんて
Next Time: Tempestuous Change.